* Services
    
    Close Services Open Services
* Event Rentals
    
    Close Event Rentals Open Event Rentals
* About
    
    Close About Open About

Dumpsters Recycling Services Site Services Landscape Materials Hauling

[* Dumpster Rentals and Roll-Offs](https://www.dtgrecycle.com/services/dumpsters/)[Find the perfect fit for any project:

* Construction
* Commercial
* Events
* Special Projects

Plus Swing & Mosquito Cans when space is limited!](https://www.dtgrecycle.com/services/dumpsters/)

* Have a lot to recycle? Look into our dumpster options.

* Need recycling at your next event? We got you.

[* Portable Restrooms & Trailers](https://www.dtgrecycle.com/services/portables/)[Additional Site Services:

* Drywall Scrapping
* Sweeping
* Fencing
* De-icing
* Snow Plowing

* View All](https://www.dtgrecycle.com/services/site-services/)

* From clearview red to sof’fall, you’re sure to find the right mulch material you need for your landscaping project.

[#### A SIZE FOR EVERY LOAD:

* Gondola | End/Side Dump | Dry Van | Lowboy | Box Truck | Flat bed](https://www.dtgrecycle.com/services/hauling/)

[* Portable Restrooms & Trailers](https://www.dtgrecycle.com/services/portables/)[* Dumpster Rentals](https://www.dtgrecycle.com/services/dumpsters/)[Partner with DTG on your next Recycling Event:

* Fundraising Collection Events
* Metal Collection Events
* E-Waste Collection Events

* Learn More](https://www.dtgrecycle.com/services/community-events/)

Search

Search 

Close this search box.

Privacy Policy
==============

### Who we are

Our website address is: https://dtgrecycle.com.

### What personal data we collect and why we collect it

#### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

#### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

#### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed. If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

#### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### Text Messaging

By providing your phone number to DTG, you agree and acknowledge that DTG may send text messages to my wireless phone number for any purpose. Message and data rates my apply. We will only send one SMS as a reply to you, and you will be able to Opt-out by replying “STOP”.

### Who we share your data with

If you request a password reset, your IP address will be included in the reset email.

#### Text Messaging

No mobile information will be shared with third parties/affiliates for marketing/promotional purposes. All the above categories exclude text messaging originator opt-in data and consent; this information will not be shared with any third parties.

### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

Recycling Services

Site Services

Additional Services

About & Support

|

Copyright 2024 DTG Recycle
